WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Hey.
Are you all right?
All your stuff was gone, so I thought...
I'm fine.
Well, what happened? Did
your sister do something or...
Henry, I'm leaving.
- What?
- I can't stay here.
Believe me, I'm tempted.
Even though the food fuckin' sucks.
You can't. You can't.
I need your help.
- You don't.
- You're wrong.
I fucked up.
I fucked up like you have no idea,
and everything is worse, and I can't.
I can't. I can't do this on my own.
- Yes, you can.
- No.
You can.
You're stronger than you think.
Something else.
Something I need to tell you.
Okay.
I don't want what happened
to me to happen to you.
I've always wanted you to
have choice and freedom,
shit I didn't have.
I owe you that.
I haven't been honest
with you about everything.
A while ago you...
You asked if I knew
where your father was,
and... I said I didn't, but...
That was a lie.
Your dad is dead.
S... What?
I should have told you
before, but I couldn't.
- That's not...
- You wouldn't have listened to me,
and I wanted to help you,
to make things right...
That's not... that's not possible.
It's not. It's not possible.
No, no, you don't know.
You don't know, because I...
I have been talking to him.
Like, he and I...
He left me a message
yesterday. He's looking for me.
He's been looking for me
this whole fucking time.
I'm sorry.
Dad?
Dad!
Simon?
Dad, please!
Henry.
How do you know about this place?
This is my...
this is my dad's cabin.
No.
It's my cabin.
Henry...
I killed him.
It happened a long time ago,
before I even knew you existed, I...
No. No.
That doesn't make any sense, because...
My body has been taking me here.
I've been dreaming about him.
We... we're connected.
He is here! He has to be here!
Your dad is here, in a way.
It's where I buried him.
No.
Dad?
Hank.
Oh, Hank.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's okay, it's okay.
Everything is gonna be okay.
Why?
Huh?
I did what I thought was right.
Your dad, he wasn't like us.
He wasn't a teleporter.
He was an Inactive.
And he was bitter about it.
He made a choice.
He was gonna tell whoever
would listen to him
about people like us.
I couldn't let that happen.
It was my job not to let that happen.
Be quiet.
Daddy?
He was dangerous.
If he would've known what
you would've become...
No.
Please.
I have a family.
Me too.
I trusted you.
You're a fucking liar!
You're a liar!
Fucking liar!
You let me think...
You let me think he was
alive this whole time
when you knew... you knew what you did!
You knew!
You knew the whole...
I'm sorry.
I need him.
Henry...
My dad...
You took him from me.
Ahhh!
Henry, I...
Ahh!
Help.
Henry...
Why?
Huh?
What the fuck were you doing with me?
I...
I care about you.
Henry, Henry!
Please...
I'm done.
I told you not to call me.
Your brother's dead.
Henry...
He finally told you.
Keep this phone.
If you ever need anyth...
I woke and you were gone.
I couldn't stay.
What I asked of you was unfair.
But I'm here now to make amends.
To act as a witness on your behalf.
This is not where you belong.
But it is.
Confessing to a crime you did not commit
will not provide relief
for your past sins.
It's not about that.
This is my path to salvation.
This is my purpose.
What purpose can you
possibly serve from a cell?
I know you, Lucas Boone.
And you know me.
I care for you.
Job 4:15.
"Fear came upon me, and trembling,
which made all my bones to shake.
Then a spirit passed before my face... "
"And the hair of my flesh stood up.
It stood still...
but I could not discern
the form thereof:
an image was before mine eyes."
This is your purpose?
An angel?
- I don't understand.
- I'm protecting her.
Her?
So this angel is alive?
She... she came to you?
Why would an angel want this for you?
She doesn't.
I came to this on my own.
Lucas, if you are here
to protect this angel,
does that mean she is the
one who killed your father?
Maybe she just lost it.
In the barn?
Where Nikolai dissolved
Bill Boone's body?
What if he did something to her?
That's not possible.
Nikolai left Reston.
At least that's what Henry said.
So what does that mean?
- Do you think Henry could've...
- No.
- Henry would never hurt Anna.
- I don't know.
I mean, she convinced
Lucas to confess for her.
How do you know that?
Townes.
My dad...
He's dead.
- What?
- Henry...
I feel so stupid.
I should've known.
'Cause if he was alive, he
would've found me, right?
I mean, he would've,
like, knocked on my door,
but he couldn't.
He couldn't, because
Nikolai fucking killed him.
Nikolai?
This whole time, I thought
that I was gonna see him again.
But he's been dead,
like, most of my life.
Henry, whose blood is that?
What else happened?
He killed my dad.
Look, I didn't mean to, but I
couldn't just let him, like...
He took him from me!
Jenna, you know.
You know what this feels like.
I mean, with your mom, like...
I lost him, and he...
he fucking deserved it!
He deserved it!
What about Anna? What happened to her?
What?
Did you kill her too?
- Where did you get that?
- The barn.
Here.
It's fine. Just give it to me.
No, why? So you can destroy it?
No, of course not.
Where the hell is she?
- What did you do?
- Nothing!
- Henry, did you hurt her?
- No!
She's not fucking dead! Sh...
I just...
I just... I took her somewhere.
I had to!
She found out everything, and
I was... I was protecting us.
- Oh, my God.
- Where did you take her?
Anna's a good person.
She's not like Bill or Nikolai.
This, this is not...
heroes don't do this!
I'm gonna fix it.
- Just give me the phone.
- No.
Jenna, come on! Someone could trace it!
If Anna's okay, it doesn't matter.
Jenna, just...
- Give it to me... Jenna.
- No!
- Let go!
- Stop it!
- Just let go!
- No!
- Stop it!
- You don't get it!
You don't fucking get it!
- Ah!
- You're sick!
Henry, there's something wrong with you!
- That's not true!
- You're a fucking monster!
Don't fucking say that!
Like Nikolai!
Nikolai killed Sam too, didn't he?
You knew!
You knew, and you lied to me.
No. Please... please, just turn it off.
Just turn it off.
I believed in you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. Please...
Please.
- Please, Townes.
- Get out of my room.
- Townes...
- Get out now!
I'm gonna bring her back, okay?
I'm gonna fix it. I
promise I'm gonna fix it.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna fix all of it!
Anna?
Anna!
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Anna?
Mom?
Shit.
Thank you.
We'll see you next week. Thank you.
Goodnight.
God bless. Goodnight.
Thank you.
Mrs. Boone?
It's Mrs. Jacobson.
Is there something I can help you with?
I'm concerned about your son, Lucas.
I fear he may be
following the wrong path.
I'm sorry. How do you know him?
We belong to the same church.
I saw him this morning.
He seems consumed with
a particular young woman.
I'm hoping you can help me find her.
I believe she's connected
to your ex-husband.
You know her...
I'm sorry, I can't help
you. I have to get back...
Mrs. Jacobson, please.
Do not give up on him.
I know all too well what
it's like to lose a son.
Mine died too soon.
But death is not the
only way to lose a child.
A boy needs his mother.
Now, please...
who is the girl?
I don't know. I saw this place.
It looked decent. The people were nice.
And they have egg rolls
which maybe is a sign.
Henry?
You all right?
Yes, yeah.
I don't know if you noticed,
but I got some new bowls.
I mean, they're just plastic,
but they're nice plastic, right?
And they're ours.
You know, I was thinking,
like, after everything
that's happened...
Maybe we should just go.
- Go where?
- Anywhere.
I know this is a lot at once.
But it's not the end.
It's gonna get better. It has to.
We're just...
we're deep in the shit of,
like, a bad thing, and...
But we have each other.
And we're gonna get through it together.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey, what if we have dinner in bed?
Dinner in bed is always better, right?
Come on. Come on.
We can pick out a movie on your laptop.
You know, but maybe...
maybe something a little more
Romy and Michele and a little less
Requiem for a Dream.
Just saying.
Here.
Hey.
You know I love you, right?
And I'm proud of you.
I love you too.
All right, let's see what we got.
This isn't me.
I mean, I don't...
I don't even remember writing this.
I thought what I turned in was...
I don't know.
Just, I want to go to college.
And I want to have a future, so...
please, just tell me what
to do, and I'll do it.
I'll rewrite every essay,
I'll retake every test.
- I'll...
- And then what?
What do you mean?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Totally. I'm fine.
I mean, no, like,
because of this, but...
Is there anything else going on at home?
I know what happened with Bill Boone
and your dad's girlfriend.
Yeah, that's o... that's okay.
I mean... I mean...
it's not, but... but it is.
It's fine. I'm fine.
Just give me another chance.
I mean... you know me.
I'm a straight-A student.
I'm not this person. This isn't me.
You've said that a couple of times now.
Look, Jenna,
if you keep ignoring
what's going on with you,
that something is going on,
then things like this
will keep happening.
You wrote those essays.
You failed a number of your tests.
No one else. You.
It's okay not to be okay.
But ignoring it won't
make it any less real.
Hey, what's up? You need something?
Uh, the housekeeper wants
to move to Wednesdays,
so I thought we could switch your PT
so that you didn't
have to work around her.
Okay, cool. Whatever.
Uh, Mom, I'm in the middle of a game.
Okay.
What?
When I was a sophomore in
college, I dated a swimmer.
Uh, not for long,
and "dating" is probably
too strong a word,
but we went out a few times.
He was older than me,
but only by a year.
Anyway, uh...
we... we were at a party...
one night, and we were drinking.
But not a lot.
Um... and we ended up
in one of the rooms.
I don't even remember how, but...
And we were kissing.
And then it got to a point where I...
tried to stop it.
Politely at first, and then...
less so, but he didn't listen.
After that, this boy
and I stopped talking.
We never talked about
how we stopped talking.
I would see him
around the campus here and there, and...
every time, I, uh...
You see, my generation, we didn't
talk about this sort of thing.
I knew right away how it made me feel.
It just took longer to put a word to it.
To realize that what happened to me...
was rape.
I've never told anybody what happened.
Not your father.
Not Robert.
I don't know if I was afraid, or...
ashamed, or...
Then why are you telling me?
I think you know why.
I don't have a fucking clue, actually.
Then why won't you look at me?
Get the fuck out of my room.
In the end, you have to
live with what you've done.
It'll be between you and
God, and you can't escape Him.
What are you doing here?
You okay?
Are you okay?
Yeah, of course.
Jesus.
This is so fucked up.
I'm the one who should be in here.
Not you... I'm the one
who should be in here.
I'm gonna tell them... I'm
gonna tell them the truth.
I'm gonna tell them that it was me,
and we're gonna get you out of here.
- Henry, no, no. No.
- Yes.
This is what I want.
And I get it, I do.
I have been where you
are, questioning who I was,
believing there was no good in me,
but the very fact that
you're questioning it...
that means there is good in you.
I am... I am not an angel, Lucas.
I'm not.
I let you believe that I was
so that you would help me, but I am not.
I am a bad and selfish person.
Hey. Hey, hey.
You are not.
You're not.
What, you think all angels
are perfect and shit?
You gotta read the Bible,
because that's not what they are,
and that is not who I think you are.
I'm not that fuckin' crazy, Henry.
I'm not.
I killed your father.
You also walked through
fire without getting burned.
Jesus Christ.
- Sorry, I'm just...
- I know. I know.
It's a lot to take in.
I...
I don't... I don't know
what you want from me.
what I'm supposed to do.
Could you please...
Look, it took me getting away from here
and all my family shit
to finally see clearly,
to see what I was meant
for, but I know it now.
I fuckin' know it right in here.
And I've got faith
that if you can just
clear all this noise...
that you'll know too.
The Lord will open a
path for you, Henry.
But you gotta open your eyes to see.
You shouldn't be here.
You gotta go.
- Okay?
- Lucas.
Wait. Come on.
Hey. Just...
Remember that doing what's right...
Isn't always what's easy.
Hey.
That was a really long meeting.
Yeah, I've... I've been
driving around for a while.
Okay, so? How did it go?
Did you guys come up with a plan?
You gonna get your grades back up?
We mostly just talked about me.
Cool.
Okay. Got it.
That's it?
- What do you want me to say?
- I don't know.
More than that.
Come on, Jenna, I...
It feels like I can't
win with you. You...
I'm trying to make things right.
I'm trying to put you first,
try to get you out of this mess,
- get you back to your old self...
- What does that mean?
I don't know. I don't... ah...
- I'm just talking.
- No, you do know.
You're just not saying it.
That... I can't keep
doing this with you.
- You make it so hard.
- How do I make it hard?
You're afraid.
You're afraid to talk about Mom.
You're afraid to get mad and,
like, actually feel things,
and you're afraid to know who I am.
Like, really know me.
That's not true. Not true.
Aren't you still trying
to figure out who you are?
I mean, you're just 17.
Right.
- Look who I found.
- Mom, you have to knock.
Hi.
I like your room.
It's bigger in person.
It's larger than Megan's room too.
Mom?
Some privacy?
Oh, yes.
Sorry. Of course.
But game night starts in ten,
and we don't hold your
spot if you're late.
I'm just kidding.
I... That's a joke.
Ah.
But seriously, ten minutes.
Your father and I
will shuffle the board.
I have something important to tell you.
Is it about the allergens here?
Because your mom already said that...
Nope, it's actually highly
sensitive information.
But I need your permission
before I say more,
because I don't want to
burden you with my problems
unless you want to be burdened.
I love you, Townes.
Whatever you need,
whatever's going on,
I'm in.
All right.
So...
For some time now, I've been
acting as a sidekick to a superhero.
- Oh.
- I know.
It's been very exciting, but...
Then something terrible happened.
Really terrible, and...
now I think maybe I've
actually been a henchman,
serving not a hero but a villain.
I... I don't know what I am or...
or who I'm meant to be.
All I know is, I need to
try and make things right.
Lives are on the line.
- Okay.
- And...
I want you to be my partner.
Not a sidekick.
But my equal in this fight,
if there is a fight.
But hopefully there's not, and if
there is, it's nothing too physical.
Um, yeah, I hope so too.
Yeah.
Well, good, great.
Thank you.
Mm.
I love you too, by the way.
I forgot to say it before.
Okay, there's a lot to explain,
but our first mission is time-sensitive.
I need you to help me find someone.
She could be anywhere in the world.
Dad's gone?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry for everything.
I think I let you down.
I know that this isn't what you wanted.
This isn't who you wanted to be.
And I'm just...
I just don't know what to do anymore.
What do I do?
Keep Mom safe.
I did.
I am. I mean...
Everyone that could hurt her is gone.
Maybe it's time to go.
I can't.
She needs us.
And I would come back to her.
I always come back to her.
Not if you break it.
But I...
And how would I do that
without hurting her?
Megan? It's Jenna.
Jenna? Hi! How's it going?
It's good.
- I'm good.
- Well, what's up?
Well, actually I was...
calling to...
see if you had Kate's number.
I... I hung out with
her at Darcy's party,
and I kinda...
you know, I... I didn't
get to say goodbye.
- Wait, she said that?
- Yeah!
Great.
That's great.
So do you think you
could text me her number?
Thanks. Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Hey.
Where've you been?
You okay, honey?
What's wrong?
My dad's dead.
- What?
- Simon is dead.
Are you sure?
I don't understand.
When did he...
He didn't abandon us, Mom.
He didn't want to leave.
He just didn't have a choice.
How do you know all this?
Baby?
Henry?
Why didn't you know?
Why am I the one who
had to figure it out?
I've asked you about him
so many times, and you just wouldn't...
you didn't care.
Honey, that's not true.
You let me think he
didn't want to know me.
But he did.
He loved me. He loved us.
And if you gave a shit about me,
or... or him or anyone but yourself,
you would've tried.
You would've fucking tried, Mom.
Can you give me a second?
'Cause you just dropped all of this
on me, and I'm trying to unders...
- No.
- Henry, I...
No! I have spent my entire
fucking life giving you a second,
picking up after you,
taking care of you,
making sure you have
everything that you need!
Okay, that's not true.
"Oh, honey, isn't this place great?
Don't you think he's nice?
Henry, this time it's
gonna be different.
Just you wait. Just you fucking wait!"
I am so sick of it, Mom!
How many schools have
you pulled me out of?
How many... how many
places have we lived?
You're always worrying about me.
Wondering why I don't
have fucking friends.
Why do you think I don't
have fucking friends?!
Do you think that this is fun for me?
Do you think that I like
moving around so much?
- I don't think that.
- Huh?
Just you and me on
another fucking adventure?
I'm sorry, okay?
You're right.
You're totally right.
I'm sorry, Henry.
I've been so selfish, honey.
And I knew that it hurt you.
Deep down I knew that.
I knew that it was hurting
you, and I did it anyway.
I'm really sorry.
It's too late.
No, it's not too late, honey.
I'm doing better. I'm
trying to do better.
I mean, you know that.
This is you trying?
I mean, this is a start, Henry.
You think because you
rented this fucking apartment
and you bought fucking bowls
that everything's gonna be okay?
Why?
Because we have each other?
Well, it's not, because
I don't want you.
I'm sorry that this isn't good enough.
I'm sorry that I can't give you more.
How many times do you
want me to apologize?
How many? I don't know
what the fuck you want.
I want you to be better than you are.
Oh, okay. That's all?
- That's all you want?
- I can't keep doing this.
I can't... can't be everything to you.
What are you doing? I don't even...
will you stop being so dramatic?
I don't want to end up like you.
I don't want you to end
up like me either, okay?
I want you to have a better life.
Then let me go.
What? No. Henry, stop.
Please, will you stop?
Will you look at me?
Will you fucking look at me?
Be honest with me.
Have you ever loved
anyone that you've dated?
Or were you just looking
for a free place to stay?
Excuse me?
Thomas is the only nice guy
that you have ever been with,
and you fucked that up too.
Want to know what I think?
I think you're just a fucking sad,
lonely woman, and no one
is ever going to love you!
What the fuck, Henry?
You think you deserve better than this,
but you don't, and you never will!
I see the way that you are.
Pining for men's attention,
asking them for help,
acting weak.
It's probably why I asked Clay
for help in the first place.
It's why I ended up in that truck.
And it's why he raped me.
- What?
- It's your fault.
What he did to me is because of you.
No, no. That is not my fault.
That is not your fault.
That is Clay Boone's fault.
Everything bad that's ever
happened to me is because of you.
- No, that is not...
- Admit it!
- Stop it, stop it!
- Mom...
- You have to st...
- I don't need you anymore!
I don't... not like you need
me, and I bet that kills you.
- No, it doesn't.
- Doesn't it?
Prove it!
Prove that you're not weak,
that you don't need me!
Get out of my fucking face. Stop it!
Or what?
- You need to calm down!
- Admit it!
- I don't need you!
- Calm down!
Say it! Come on!
- Enough!
- Let me go!
Ow!
Fuck!
All right, get out! Get the fuck out!
Go! Get the fuck out!
I never want to see you again.
Henry...
I don't... I can't...
You should've seen him.
He wasn't even remorseful.
It's okay.
- We'll figure it out.
- How?
What is there to figure out?
I know he did it.
He's a rapist.
He is your son.
I don't even know how to be around him.
What the fuck?
♪ I don't wanna tear your heart out ♪
♪ But I'm edging on a breakdown ♪
♪ I've been up and down the same route ♪
♪ Too afraid of the fall out ♪
♪ I know that we gotta quit,
you just never see it ♪
♪ Don't wanna admit it but
you're stuck in my system ♪
♪ And I just wanna clear
it like an exorcism ♪
♪ I know we got hell to pay ♪
♪ You don't wanna see it, it, it ♪
♪ You should be picking
me up in this battle ♪
me up but I'm down ♪
♪ I'm lying awake and I tremble ♪
♪ I tremble ♪
Henry?
I've been watching you for some time.
It was you.
You have no idea what you've started.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -