WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
[GENTLE MUSIC]
BILL: You took my family away from me.
Show me!
Four.
I trusted you, and you lied to me.
Three.
HENRY: No, no, no, no!
Two.
[SIGHS]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[EXHALES]
[KIMBRA'S  TOP OF THE WORLD PLAYING]
♪ On my knees, all my life ♪
♪ I've been sold a chase ♪
♪ Hustling hope for
dollars, try cope a day ♪
♪ A day ♪
♪ Under condition,
we on our way to the top ♪
♪ We got the world at our fingers ♪
♪ We make the penny drop ♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY, CHUCKLES]
♪ I'll say it loud till I mean it ♪
♪ Talk like I be the messiah ♪
♪ When I'm on top, I'm on
top, I'm on top of the world ♪
♪ See me run, see me run,
see me run with the girls ♪
♪ I'm on top, I'm on top,
I'm on top of the world ♪
♪ Need a break, then I'll
take to the top of the world ♪
♪ On my knees, all my life ♪
♪ I've been sold a chase ♪
♪ Hustling hope for
dollars, try cope a day ♪
♪ A day ♪
♪ Euphoria, I missed you
like a new treasure ♪
♪ We go so good together ♪
♪ Search all my life to find better ♪
♪ But I won't hold my breath ♪
♪ I'll just fill up and deliver ♪
♪ They got attention deficit ♪
♪ Wait for the good Lord to visit ♪
♪ All my life turned to dust ♪
Oh, no, I don't have a degree.
♪ No one knew who to trust ♪
♪ Had a chance for good life ♪
But, um, I'm a hard worker.
♪ See me on tele, see me
on billboards and banners ♪
♪ See me white picket fences ♪
♪ Now watch me
build up my palace ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha ♪
And a fast learner.
♪ Won't forget where I
started when we would ♪
♪ Pray from the gutters ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm on top, I'm on top ♪
♪ I'm on top of the world ♪
♪ Send me up, send me up with
the diamonds and pearls ♪
♪ I'm on top, I'm on top,
I'm on top of the world ♪
♪ And they can talk, they can talk ♪
♪ But I got the good word ♪
♪ Man, it's crazy,
undefined, brand-new ♪
♪ It's amazing I got high on a view ♪
♪ But tonight I'm
feeling tired and alone ♪
♪ Dear Lord, I hope we didn't go wrong ♪
♪ I think I'm winning ♪
♪ Feel like I might ♪
♪ Feels like I'm in it ♪
♪ Feel like a god ♪
[GROANS]
[CHOKING]
[GROANING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
WOMAN: I'm so sorry about that.
WOMAN: Is she all right?
MAN: Did you see that?
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GROANS]
[AMY STROUP'S MAGIC PLAYING]
[HENRY CHUCKLES]
♪ I'm sticking with you, honey ♪
♪ You make the whole world sunny ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ You got that golden heart ♪
♪ Been loving it from the start ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
[LUC'S GLOW PLAYING]
Surf's Up.
[SIGHS] Uh, do you have any... Oh.
And what about...
Parmesan is on the table.
♪ You're living dreams ♪
♪ You're living like a Kennedy ♪
♪ Isn't what you had envisioned ♪
Miss?
♪ So you're fading out ♪
These mushrooms are burnt.
They're full of carcinogens.
♪ You're fading now ♪
Okay. I'll take care of it.
GRADY: Sorry, no deliveries
today. Carryout only.
Hello?
These mushrooms have cancer.
♪ You wonder if there's
light if you could fly away ♪
♪ You're gonna leave this town ♪
♪ But you're holding out ♪
Hey, did you get ahold of Jason?
He caught whatever Casey has.
Oh, right.
Hey, did you get the Tsunami...
The Tsunami pizzas out? Yeah.
- Did you drop...
- Drop table six?
Yeah, they're good.
♪ You shine brighter
than all the others ♪
♪ You fly higher than the stars above ♪
Oh, thanks.
♪ You glow ♪
♪ Oh, you know ♪
[SIGHS] Where did all of
these people come from?
It should die down soon. [CHUCKLES]
Uh-oh.
[LAUGHTER, CHATTER]
Yeah, we're totally screwed.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
- Okay.
- [TRAFFIC WHIZZING]
[SOFT CLATTER]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Cleo.
Hi, Iris.
Um, is Greg around?
I was hoping to talk to him
about getting back on the schedule.
You know, after everything
that happened with Bill
and the dealership, I...
Which part exactly?
Iris, I did not sleep with Bill.
Come on, it was just a job.
Okay. Sorry.
I... I'm truly sorry, Cleo.
I am, but you quit, and
we had to replace you.
Well, there has to be something.
I mean, maybe I could cover some shifts
or just fill in until something...
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING SOFTLY]
I don't really know
if that's a good idea.
[SIGHS]
Hi, Cleo.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Lucas.
Sorry, I... I know...
I know it's weird just
showing up like this.
Um, I just, uh...
You following me?
No, no, I, uh...
I heard what my dad did.
Are you, uh...
I mean, how are you?
I'm okay.
Cool, good, good.
Um...
look, I just, uh...
I just want to thank you for...
everything that you
said to me in that car.
I don't know what I would
have done if you hadn't.
You were always so nice to me,
and... and I'm doing better.
I'm a better man now because of you.
And I want to thank you
for not pressing charges.
Most people, they wouldn't
be so forgiving, so...
It's not about forgiveness.
I... just want to move on.
Henry and I, we... we want to
put this whole thing behind us.
Henry.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're okay, Lucas.
Really, I am.
You too.
Lucas.
Do you know where your dad is?
You don't have to worry about him.
You're safe now.
GRADY: All right, let's
see what we got here.
$10.50,
$11.50,
$12.33.
Wow, that's really impressive.
And that's not all.
Oh.
Staci with an I and no E.
And a heart.
Are you gonna text her?
[SCOFFS] No.
She's not really my type.
Well, I got $19 even, so...
Damn it! You beat me.
I know.
Well, then that's good.
Yeah, you'll need it for all your, um...
your fancy bio textbooks, right?
Um, I'm actually thinking
of going to art school.
Art, really?
Like, uh, drawing, painting?
I do murals
on buildings, I guess.
It's like street art.
That's cool.
So like, um...
No.
It's not bad.
Really?
Mm-mm, no!
[CHUCKLES]
Well, if you squint a little, I mean...
What?
- Okay, it's not great.
- [CHUCKLES]
All right, but it's Venice.
- [LAUGHS]
- Right?
You should go see it before it sinks.
[CHUCKLES]
I mean, I got a whole list
of places I want to go see.
I mean, I'm not rich yet,
so it'll take a while,
but I'll get there.
What about you, hmm?
What about me?
Well, is there anyplace
you're itching to get to?
Um... [SIGHS]
I don't know.
I don't know, I'm kind of just, like,
getting used to life here.
MAN: The reason why most
people need snacks before...
Get back to work.
Yeah. Oh.
YVETTE: Oh, God.
That must have been,
what, ten years ago?
Yeah.
So your room at home is good to go.
I cleared out all the
swords and diamond necklaces.
Ruby's been using it
as her princess castle.
[CHUCKLING] Oh.
Kitchenware.
Thanks.
I'm gonna get a coffee.
Your, uh, machine doesn't work.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
He's worried about you.
Is that what that is?
Can't even be in the same room as me.
He still blames me
for what happened in...
Uh-uh, no.
I don't wanna hear it.
You icing me out, too?
No, look,
I just don't want to be
the middleman anymore.
[SIGHS]
I am glad you're coming home,
but you've got to at least
try to fix things with Dad.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
If you keep carrying all
this stuff around with you,
you are gonna break.
More than you already have.
[SIGHS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[SOBS]
[SOBBING]
[GRADY SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
[SINGING IN PORTUGUESE]
Shit, uh, I was just, uh...
Um, we're closed.
So we can go now.
Well, I've still got
some boxes to restock,
but you can take off.
I'll finish up.
What are you listening to?
Uh, this band out of Brazil.
Here.
[SOFT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[HUMMING ALONG]
Ooh.
[CHUCKLING] Look at your dance moves.
[CHUCKLES]
It's a little, um, lo-fi, but
that's the charm, you know?
Um, do you speak Portuguese?
- Mm-hmm, fluently.
- Really?
Mm-hmm, yeah. [SPEAKING PORTUGUESE]
It means, uh, "Please
speak more slowly."
It's a... it's a good one to know.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, you know how you asked me, um,
like, where I would go if I could?
Mm-hmm.
I think Barcelona.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can see that.
Yeah, the museums, the art scene.
Yeah, I mean, yes,
but it's not, like, really about that.
Um, my mom and I used
to move around a lot,
and we'd always, like, pass
through these small towns
on the way to somewhere else,
and people were always asking us
where we were coming from,
and my mom would say Barcelona,
which I guess was probably easier
than saying, like, we were running away
from some asshole in
Grafton, New Hampshire,
or wherever, but...
yeah.
It sort of became like a game.
Like, we would find a diner
and we'd order Shirley Temples,
and we'd tell the waitress
that they weren't as good
as the ones we had in Barcelona.
And I don't even know if they
have Shirley Temples in Barcelona,
but I don't know what they have there.
So yeah, Barcelona.
You'll have to send me a postcard.
Deal.
Hey, um, thank you for covering today.
Oh, yeah, it was fun.
Yeah, I got to spend time with
you, so I'm not complaining.
[CHUCKLES]
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
- HENRY: Sorry.
- GRADY: I got it.
HENRY: Ow.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- HENRY: Please. I'm being serious.
- CLAY: Don't worry.
HENRY: Ow.
HENRY: I don't want... please.
-  Please.
- [MUFFLED] What's wrong?
CLAY: You'll get wet soon.
HENRY: Get the... get the...
CLAY: Jesus, Henry.
GRADY: Henry.
HENRY: Get the fuck off of me!
[OBJECTS RATTLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[OBJECTS CRASHING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [WHOOSHING]
Henry?
[WHOOSHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
CLEO: Henry, I thought you were at work.
I gotta go. I'm gonna be late.
Yeah, so then I installed
these really cool RGB lights,
and also this arm has a rotating wrist,
which is awesome.
Cool.
Hey, is that the Enterprise NCC-1701-E?
Okay, some people think
it's the Enterprise D.
With that engine chamber?
[CHUCKLES]
[ALARM BEEPING]
Oh.
I have to go to bed,
but my mom wants to know
if you have any dietary
restrictions or food allergies.
I already told her, no walnuts.
We're good, then.
Are you sure you're cool with me
crashing your family game night?
Yes, my parents like
when I have company,
but you can't be game
master on your first visit.
And if we play Settlers of Catan,
you can't build a road
through an enemy's settlement.
It's a common mistake.
Why would I waste my time building roads
when I know the Knight Cards
get me just as many victory points
and I control the Robber?
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLES] I'll see you Saturday.
I love you.
I love you, too.
[COMPUTER CHIMES]
For fuck's sake, kid, stop
clicking on random links.
No, I'm not hacking your computer again.
Go away! I'm not a part of this anymore!
If you're talking, I can't hear you,
because if you are
watching this, I'm dead,
probably for a couple days now,
if this fail-safe shit actually worked.
All my other contacts are dead, too,
so you're the closest thing I
have to a protégé by default,
and I'm leaving you my life's work.
Well, the work of my middle age.
Everything I have on the teleporters
and their operations.
Obviously they got to me
before I could stop them.
Listen. [SIGHS]
I didn't plan on getting
involved in this shit.
I was just in the wrong
place at the wrong time,
and I decided to do the right thing.
Just don't let this
fuck you over like me.
No family, no friends.
Christ, it's not lost on me
that I'm sending my last words
to some kid I met fucking once.
Okay, I'm sending you
encrypted coordinates
and a lock code.
I want you to memorize
it and then delete them,
and then delete this.
And good luck, kid.
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[WHOOSHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
[TENSE MUSIC]
What happened?
Had a panic attack and
ended up in my fucking room.
Somebody hurt you?
No.
No one did anything.
I just...
I just felt like I was
back in that fucking truck
like the first time, and I'm just mad,
because I thought I was past this shit.
It gets worse before it gets
better, if that's any comfort.
It's not.
What if your sister uses that
fake room against me and...
I took care of it, I told you.
Yeah, but what does that mean?
It's fine.
We wouldn't be here
if it wasn't, trust me.
I'm just...
[GENTLE MUSIC]
I painted my room.
I took down all my shit.
I thought I was different.
I felt different.
You're tethered to your room
because of what it represents,
not what it looks like.
It doesn't represent anything.
It's a fucking room.
It's where you feel safe.
Without a place to go
back to, in the beginning,
we'd be lost.
At least that's how I've...
rationalized it for myself.
So what's yours?
Well...
apartment I grew up in,
but I don't go back there anymore.
Why not?
Something happened,
and it stopped feeling like it used to.
So I can break it,
this... tether connection, whatever.
I did, but it's not an easy trade,
losing safety for freedom.
[SIGHS]
Why do our bodies do such weird shit?
I don't know.
What do you think we are?
Fuck if I know.
Are you not even curious at all?
I'm not sure if it'd
change anything if I knew.
So that's it?
Hey...
you know more than I
did when I was your age,
and I didn't have somebody
who'd been through this shit before.
I had an uncle
who was scared of me.
Thought I was Moroi,
a ghost.
Not exactly an inspiring thought.
What about an angel?
Do you feel like an angel?
No.
Yeah.
Me neither.
FISHER: After Mr. Boone shot you...
CLEO: I don't remember anything.
I woke up in the hospital.
FISHER: And you didn't
regain consciousness
- at any point before that?
- HENRY: Cops?
CLEO: No, not until after the surgery.
Oh, Henrietta.
Sheriff Fisher.
CLEO: Apparently there have been
some new developments in the case.
You mind if I ask you
a couple questions?
Is there a better time to do this?
It's a school night.
Oh, and I appreciate that.
We have reason to believe
there was a struggle
here at the house.
I already talked to
Anna Hulce about that.
Unfortunately the former sheriff
wasn't in her best state of
mind to execute her duties,
so I'm taking over.
Well, you've already
took our statements.
Yes, but we want to wrap the case up.
Yeah, keep things local
before the feds get involved.
I imagine you folks
want... want that as well.
See, the truth is, Henry,
we got 25 guys out there,
and they are working day in and day out.
They're combing the
woods, knocking on doors,
but they don't have any leads.
I'm just wondering if
I'm wasting my time.
Hey.
What are you suggesting?
[TENSE MUSIC]
What happened to Bill Boone?
Are you serious?
I don't believe this.
Bill came into our house with a gun.
He shot me and abducted my daughter.
We are the victims here.
How 'bout this, huh?
I'll take a quick look around,
and then we'll get settled.
Have you got a warrant?
Well, there's no need
for that yet, Mr. Hope.
I'm just keeping things friendly.
Oh, okay, well, in that
case, I will ask you
with a big, friendly smile,
get the fuck out of our house.
All right.
I'll get that warrant.
I'll be seeing you soon.
You folks have a good night, now.
THOMAS: Yes, yes, thank you.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
What are we gonna do? They're
gonna search our house.
It's okay. They won't find anything.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm, like, 90% sure.
Okay, no, I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
How can you keep doing this?
I don't have a choice.
What if... what if we
just tell them the truth?
No, not the cops. Our parents.
If we tell them about Bill,
we have to tell them about me.
Okay, but your mom loves you.
She'll accept who you are.
I don't even know what I am.
And she already treats me like there's
something fucking wrong with me.
If she knew the truth,
she would never be able
to look at me again.
Maybe she'd think you're so much cooler.
How would I even say it?
"I teleport."
Or, "I'm a teleporter."
Nikolai said that we might be ghosts.
And Lucas thinks I'm an angel.
Wait, Lucas Boone?
Yeah, he found me at the dance.
What? Why didn't you say anything?
Because it's... it's fine, I think.
He just wanted to talk
or check on me, protect me.
I don't fucking know.
Apparently he's religious
now, like, really religious.
And he thinks you're an angel.
[SIGHS]
Could be worse.
He could think I was the devil.
Right.
Jenna.
I... I will figure something out,
and we will get through
this like we always do,
but we have to stick together.
Please, don't say anything to anyone.
I'm not ready for what that might do
to all of us.
Okay, I won't.
Okay.
But the cops aren't gonna just go away.
I know.
[GLASSES SINGING] ♪ Now it's over ♪
♪ Yeah-ah-ah ♪
[SLURPING]
Hey, what level clearance
did they give you?
Orange.
Right. [CHUCKLES] Right.
I forgot, it's been so
long since my training.
What level are you?
Orange.
Okay, so...
the same.
It's not an easy job. It's pretty hard.
My last partner couldn't cut it.
Now he's at corporate pushing papers.
[SCOFFS]
So, like, a promotion?
No, I mean, that's
not what he called it.
That would be a promotion
if he's at corporate now.
It's not...
[LOUD CLATTER]
Fuck was that?
- Stay here.
- I'll come with you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Rookie, I got it.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[SCUFFLING]
[GLASSES GROANING]
[GROANS] [WHISPERING] Behind you.
Who the fuck are you?
GLASSES: She's my new partner.
Gun.
Where's the Factor?
Oh, come on, man, you
know we can't do that.
Requires a call-in. We're radio silent.
[GROANING]
- [WHOOSHING]
- [GUNSHOT]
Oh, fuck!
Oh, God.
[GROANING]
[SIGHS]
Oh, fuck you. [GROANING]
Factor.
Elaine will kill me.
Okay, okay.
You motherfucker.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hurry.
That's all we have left.
I'd stop waiting on Elaine and
start looking for a new job.
Dick!
[WHOOSHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[EERIE MUSIC]
Shit.
[BELL RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey.
Are you okay?
Um, I don't know.
Last night...
last night, I got a message.
Excuse me, Jenna, can I
steal you for a minute?
Um...
Sure, of course.
I'll call you later?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Can I ask what this is about?
We'll explain soon enough.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Miss Hope.
Please have a seat.
Am I in trouble?
LUCAS: Hey.
Hey.
I'm glad that you called.
- Do you wanna...
- Yeah.
[LUCAS SIGHS]
It's a shitty feeling, right?
Looking at me...
and seeing him.
Yeah.
Yeah, I get it.
With Esther... Esther
Miller, Amos' mom...
[SIGHS] I'd see him all the time.
It's permanent.
Taking a life.
That's...
that's my fault, too, Lucas.
I'm... I'm the one who
pointed him out, so...
It's not your fault.
It's not, Henry.
Listen, I need your help.
Yeah, of course. Anything.
What... what do you need?
This cop Fisher came by the house,
and he was asking questions.
I think he's close to figuring
out what happened to your dad.
Uh, okay.
What does he know?
He found blood,
um, your dad's blood,
and I don't know what else, but
he's getting a search warrant.
Could you call him and say
that you've seen your dad?
That he came to you
after he left my house
and that he's, um...
that he's alive and out there somewhere?
I think he'll believe you.
Yeah, but where do I say he went?
And then what happens when
they don't find him there?
I don't know. I'm just...
This is gonna buy me some
time, so that's all I need.
And then what?
Maybe he'll keep going
in that direction.
I don't know. I just need to get him
off my back so that I can figure it out.
There's another way...
To stop Fisher...
Just make... all of this
go away.
But you need to trust me.
ANNA: Shit.
We, uh... we need more packing tape.
Okay.
Take a walk with me.
Look, I know what you're thinking.
I'm a disgrace to the uniform.
I messed up at home with Ortez.
I came here. I made it worse.
I know you blame me for Ortez's death.
I think about him every day.
I didn't see what happened.
I wish I did, but I didn't.
My struggle with you, Anna,
is not with what you saw
or didn't see, it's with what you know.
You didn't trust your instincts.
You didn't assert
what you knew was true.
I didn't see William shoot
Ortez. That's the truth.
What was I supposed to...
What truth is more important?
The fact that a kid was shot
in cold blood for the color of his skin
or that you were facing the
other way when it happened?
Well, if I had said something,
what difference would it have made?
My partner still would have gotten off,
whether I saw him or not.
I would have lied under oath.
Either way, I would have let you down.
I didn't raise you to make me proud.
I raised you to figure out
what that means for yourself.
I'm sorry, Anna, but you're
held to a different standard.
So the choices you make
will always be harder,
but you have to make them.
You left the city with regrets.
Don't leave here the same way.
No matter what people are saying,
you are gonna have
to live with yourself.
♪ Baby, you see ♪
♪ You're so right for me ♪
♪ And I'm right for you ♪
♪ I love the things you do ♪
♪ Like sweet-tasting wine ♪
♪ Your lips are so divine ♪
♪ Your loving turns me on ♪
♪ My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ That's why I'm never
gonna let you go ♪
♪ Never gonna let you go ♪
♪ Babe, I'm never gonna let you go ♪
♪ No, no, never gonna let you go ♪
♪ Baby, never gonna let you go ♪
♪ Never gonna let you go ♪
♪ Babe, I'm never gonna let you go ♪
♪ No, no, never gonna let you go ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey, my car is making
that clicking sound again.
♪ Never gonna let you go ♪
Hey, now.
[THOMAS CHUCKLES]
What's the occasion?
To celebrate your car
making that clicking sound.
How was your day?
[GROANS]
Aw, come here. Welcome home. Mm.
[PHONE RINGING]
I should probably get that,
just in case it's a job.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- This is nice.
- Yeah.
Girls, dinner, come on!
CLEO: Hello?
THOMAS: Henry.
Madam.
Jenna.
Madame.
Ooh, sparkling cider.
♪ Never gonna let you go ♪
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
♪ Babe, I'm never gonna let you go ♪
CLEO: Bye. Thank you.
Bill Boone is dead.
[TENSE MUSIC]
What?
Lucas just confessed to killing him.
[CLEO SIGHS]
I just saw Lucas.
What? When?
The other day at The Yolk.
He seemed like... I don't know. I...
I can't believe it.
I think that it's a good thing
that Bill's not out there
anymore, that we are safe.
Yeah.
That this is finally,
finally over.
[CIDER POURING]
Right.
CLEO: Of course, yes.
THOMAS: Okay.
Okay, then.
Now, Jenna,
how... how was school today?
I'm failing.
[CHUCKLES]
What?
I'm failing school.
They told me today.
Okay, how... wait.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
They told you that you're
failing what subject?
All of them.
I don't know. I don't
know how it happened.
What if I don't get into
Colgate or... anywhere?
I mean, I had a plan.
Jenna, it's gonna be okay.
Grades aren't, like,
the end of the world.
Yeah, maybe to you, they're not,
but I actually have a future, Henry.
- THOMAS: Whoa, sweetie...
- CLEO: Jenna...
No, I know my life is
some sort of joke to you.
That's not what I was saying.
This is your fault.
What?
Everybody takes care of you,
and you don't even give a shit.
I mean, my own dad told
me to take care of you.
And that's my fault?
Yes.
Henry dragged Jenna off to a party.
Henry was acting out.
Jenna followed suit.
I took care of it.
Followed suit?
What?
Well, come on.
She must have had some influence.
Dude, I'm sitting right here.
Why do you say that?
Oh, sneaking off to parties,
failing classes.
Jenna was not like this before.
[SCOFFS] Wow, okay.
No, he's right. Everything
was fine before you got here.
Jenna, what the fuck?
This is your shit.
Don't try to make this about me.
Right, I'm sorry, that's your job.
I didn't ask you to,
like, hang out with me
or help me or whatever the fuck it is
you think that I'm doing.
I have no choice!
I mean, you live in my house.
Jenna.
Hey, don't.
So you can criticize my daughter,
but I can't interrupt yours?
I just want to hear her out.
It's not a bad thing to listen.
- As if I don't?
- No. [SIGHS]
All I'm saying is that someone
has to maintain a sense
of normalcy around here.
[SCOFFS] What the hell
do you mean by that?
Nothing.
Nothing, it's just... you
know, it's a lot sometimes.
What is, being with me?
No, no, just parenting everybody.
Jesus, Thomas, you act
like I'm not as good as you.
No, we... Cleo, we just have
a different version of good.
Are you fucking serious?
Dude, lay off.
- He's not talking to you.
- Here we go.
- Here we go?
- Yeah, this is exactly what I'm talking about.
The two of you are going at it again.
You two love to pick fights.
Will you please keep her out of this?
- She's already in it!
- You know what? Fuck this.
Yeah, run away. That'll
make everything better.
Whatever works for you, Henry.
Okay.
What did you say to him?
Huh? To get him to
blow up his whole life.
Is it the same shit you say to me?
Jenna, I am not responsible for you.
Just like you are not
responsible for me.
Aren't I, though?
Who else is going to keep your secrets?
You know what? I am so tired
of telling your stupid fucking lies.
You... you made me into someone I'm not,
and you just use people
up and spit them out.
What the fuck? No, I don't.
You know exactly what you are.
You're just afraid to admit it.
Jenna, you better fucking watch it.
- Or what?
- THOMAS: Hey!
CLEO: What the hell is going on?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Well?
- Henry's...
- Jenna's gay.
[STAMMERS]
Jenna...
THOMAS: Henry, give her a
little bit of space, Jesus!
What is wrong with
you? Look what you did.
What she did? They're
both out of control.
How come only one of them is crying?
You are so fucking blind,
Thomas, you know that?
Henry, come on, let's go.
Un-fucking-believable.
[CELL DOORS CLANG]
[KEYS JANGLE]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
Wendy, hi. Everything okay?
Lucas?
He what?
[SIGHS] No, hold on. Slow down. I...
No, I didn't know. I've...
I've been on leave.
Let me find out everything I can.
[MUSIC PLAYING SOFTLY OVER RADIO]
Is that Jenna?
No, it's work.
You okay?
You're not a bad
influence or a bad person.
Really.
I just totally betrayed Jenna.
So that's true? Jenna's gay?
I should never have said that.
She trusted me.
I say things I shouldn't
say all the time.
I know.
We Coles women are complicated.
I think you mean flawed.
Yeah, but flawed together.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
TOWNES: My name is
Townes Atticus Linderman,
and if you're watching
this, I'm probably dead.
I'm about to embark on something new,
something that I hope
will help more than hurt,
but I'm not sure.
[ELECTRONIC ROCK MUSIC]
There are things I've seen that
I never knew were possible,
though I always hoped they were.
Some people might want
to use it to hurt others,
and I just...
I can't let that happen.
♪ ♪
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
TOWNES: So if this leads to my end,
to whoever's watching this,
tell my parents and
Megan I'll miss them.
I hope you understand my choices.
Jenna,
it was a pleasure serving by your side.
You are my friend,
even if you are stubborn
and opinionated.
And, Henry Coles,
thank you for trusting me
and for confiding in me.
I hope whatever killed me helped you...
or people like you or people in general.
And, Zoe...
You made me brave.
I love you.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Why did you cover your art?
I don't know.
I guess I was feeling stuck...
needed a change.
Did it help?
Not really.
I'm sorry things have
been so chaotic lately.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
You deserve to have a
home that feels secure.
We moved around so much.
I've tried to give you that, but...
I'm gonna do better, Henry. I promise.
It's you.
What is?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Doesn't matter where we go.
This room doesn't matter.
It's you. You're my home.
You're what makes me feel safe.
I'm tethered to you.
Come here.
[NELSON CAN'S  BREAK
DOWN YOUR WALLS PLAYING]
♪ You've been holding back ♪
♪ For a lifetime ♪
♪ Without even knowing
why you're so afraid ♪
♪ Every day ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -